

CONTACT ME AT



Lawsondavey642@gmail.com



+64 02108699919



9 Leitch StreetSomerfield, Christchurch 8024

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Building Computers

•••• HTML & CSS

•••• Gaming

•••• Streaming

AWARDS RECEIVED

- The Field Trophy. For perseverance & courage in the face of Adversity (2021)
- Cathedral Grammar 1st XI Hockey team Winning the season (2017)

LAWSON DAVEY

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hi my name is Lawson, I am a kind and very respecting person to others. I'm extremely interested in IT and computers and very interested in finance like stocks and crypto. I would love to work for you because it would help kickstart my career. I'd be able to do any job that is needed to the highest quality standard at an efficient speed. Below are just some details about myself like work experience education history and references. I would love to hear back from you thank you.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Fiverr | April 2020 - August 2021

• I used to make Minecraft severs for people all around the world use the website fiverr to post my skills. I had many great reviews saying that I was great with what I did for them. With a lot of five stars.

Company Owner

Valorteck | DEC 2021 - Present

• I have a small IT business where I help people with their IT problems and get them fixed to the higher standard This is a side job that will not affect working for you.

Charity work/Comunity service

- I helped with Gardening at hohepa Homes.
- Helped with Gardening at Burwood hospital.
- Tree Planting in the Red Zone.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

High School

Feb 2018 - present

- Digital Tech, English, History, Maths Stats and Physics
- High school qualification

NCEA level 1 complete

NCEA level 2 complete

REFEREES

Kathleen Ballin

Phone: +64 21 221 1991

Christine

Phone: +64 21 074 1784